# JANUS QUEK

# • DETAILS •

Singapore 81898717

#### mistake\_monoxide@hotmail.com

Place of birth Singapore

Nationality

Singaporean

#### o LINKS o

https://janusquek.tech/

https://linkedin.com/in/janus-quek/

#### o SKILLS o

C++

C#

Python

Ruby

Unity

Unreal Engine

Microsoft Office

Adobe Photoshop

#### LANGUAGES

English

Chinese

Japanese

## HOBBIES

Video Gaming Story Writing Music Composition

# PROFILE

Experienced in gameplay programming via C# scripting, C# scripting integration via Mono, adaptive audio technology via FMod, editor programming via IMGUI, serialization via Rapidjson, and memory management.

Attained various academic achievements and project awards during my time in Digipen.

Currently on a scholarship with The Infocomm Media Development Authority of Singapore.

# EDUCATION

# Bachelor of Science in Game Design, DigiPen Institute of Technology Singapore, Singapore

September 2018 — December 2021

GPA: 3.65

Admitted into the Director's List every semester except Spring 2021

Helped develop Howl: A Tale of Wolves in 2019:

3rd Place for Claude Comair Grand Prize for Game of the Year

**Best Sophomore Game** 

**Best Sophomore Technology** 

Finalist - Best 2D Graphics Technology

Finalist - Most Innovative Design

Helped develop Spellthief in 2018:

Best Freshman Technology

Finalist - Best 2D Physics Technology

Finalist - Best Music and Sound Design

Finalist - Best Artificial Intelligence

#### Game and Entertainment Technology, Temasek Polytechnic, Singapore

April 2013 — March 2016

# EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

#### Build & Tools Programmer Intern at Ubisoft Singapore, Singapore

May 2021 — November 2021

Worked with ELK Stack, Teamcity, WPF, and other in-house technologies

Developed analysis and visualization of build stability, automated scheduled processes, and editor features

#### National Serviceman at National Service, Singapore

October 2016 — August 2018

## Game Programmer at Temasek Polytechnic, Singapore

May 2016 — July 2016

Worked with Unity to develop Mindworks, a set of brain training games

# Programmer Intern at Bandai Namco Studios Singapore, Singapore

October 2015 — March 2016

Worked with Unreal Engine 4, WPF, and MySQL

Developed a game prototype and an employee sign-in/out system